memes.com 2015-12-11

# Privacy Policy | memes.com

Updated: November 25, 2012

Your privacy is one of our biggest concerns. Occasionally Memes.com may change its privacy policy. Memes.com encourages visitors to check this page often to check for any changes to the privacy policy. Continued use of Memes.com websites upon modification to its privacy policy will act as your acceptance of any and all changes.

## Intro

Memes.com puts your privacy at the top of our list of priorities.

This privacy policy was has been created in accordance with the privacy policy provided by wordpress.com(automattic.com) under the creative commons sharealike license.This notice is very important to any visitor of Memes.com and should be read thoroughly.

## Website Visitors and Registered Users

Memes.com collects non-personally-identifying information in a matter similar to many website operators. Information that is typically collected include but are not limited to ones such as the referring site, date and time of visit, browser, operating system, and count of returning versus new visitors. Memes.com uses this information to get a better understanding of their audience and therefore better the website as a whole. Memes.com may publish information to the general public regarding the usage of its website and or affiliate websites but will not release personally-identifying information. Information such as IP addresses or other personally-identifying information may be collected but will not be used to acquire private information on its visitors, nor will it disclose any such information other than described below.

## Aggregation of Personally-Identifying Information

A number of visitors to Memes.com decide to interact with the website in a manner where personally-identifiable information is necessary. The amount or type of information that is required will depend upon the form of interaction. In every case, Memes.com will collect such information only as is required or deemed appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with Memes.com. Memes.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other then as described below. Visitors have the ability to refuse to provide personally-identifiable information at the risk that they may be prevented from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Memes.com may analyze and collect statistics about the activities of visitors to its websites. For example, Memes.com may keep account of the most popular pages, collections, or referring sites. Memes.com may display this information publicly or share it with others. Memes.com does not release personally-identifiable information related to its statistics other then as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifiable Information

Memes.com shares potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know such information to process it on Memes.com’s behalf or to provide services to Memes.com, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose any such information to any other party except for those directly involved. Some of this potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information may be given to parties outside of your country; by using Memes.com websites, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer of such information to them. Also, in some cases we may decide to buy or sell assets. In this type of transaction, information is one of the business assets that is transferred. Additionally, if Memes.com or considerably all of its assets were acquired, or in the unfortunate event that Memes.com goes out of business or enteres bankruptcy, use information would be one of the assets that are transferred and or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that this type of transfer may occur, and that any acquirer of Memes.com may continue to use any personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, Memes.com will not lease out, rent, or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Aside from its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as explained in the previous paragraph, Memes.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required by law to do so. Memes.com will also disclose such information when it believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights or property of Memes.com, third parties or the general public. Should you be a registered user of a Memes.com website and have supplied your email address, Memes.com may send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit feedback, and or keep you informed of whats happening with Memes.com and its services. If you send a request to Memes.com either privately or through one of the websites contact tools, Memes.com reserves the right to publish it in order to assist us in clarifying, respond to your request, or to help other users with the same issue. Memes.com ensures that all measures are taken that are reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. Please be aware that if you are submitting information to “chat rooms,” “forums,” “comments” or “message boards” such information is then considered public information. In other words, you lose any and all privacy rights you may have with regards to that information. Doing so also increases the amount of unwanted communications or SPAM.

## Cookies

A cookie is information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Memes.com uses cookies to help track and identify visitors, monitor the usage of Memes.com websites and website access preferences every time the visitor returns to the site. Should a visitor refuse to have cookies placed on their computers, will have to set their browsers to refuse cookies prior to using the Memes.com websites. Users acknowledge and accept that disabling cookies may cause certain features of Memes.com websites to not function properly.

## Advertisements

Ads that appear on any of Memes.com websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may also set cookies. These cookies give the ad server the ability to recognize your computer every time they send you an online advertisement to put together information about you or anyone who uses your computer. This information allows the ad networks to, among other things, deliver advertisements targeted at the users interest. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Memes.com, but does not cover any use of cookies by advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect data when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp​](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp%E2%80%8B).

## Third Party Links

This privacy policy applies only to Memes.com and the information that is collected by its websites. This privacy policy does not apply to the conduct of other companies that Memes.com does not own or control, or employees that Memes.com does not manage. Memes.com websites may contain or promote links to other websites. Any information that you provide to, or that is obtained by, third-party organizations or websites may be subject to the privacy policy of those sites, if any at all. Please read the privacy policy of any and all third-party websites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of these third parties to abide by any and all restrictions on the disclosure of your potentially-personally and personally-identifying information. Memes.com and its affiliates shall not be liable for any wrongful use or disclosure of your potentially-identifying and or personally-identifying information by any third party.

## Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers. Memes.com ensures that reasonable measures are taken to ensure the safety of such information. 

## Choice/Opt-out

If Memes.com contacts you by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, Memes.com will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices. 

## Contact

If you have any questions or are unsure about something within the privacy policy, or the Memes.com website itself, please contact us.
